KEVIN LIN

Full-Stack Developer

New York, NY | Linkevin.0917@gmail.com | (929)920-7607 www.linkedin.com/in/kevinlin1997 | github.com/Linkevin1997

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Software Engineer who has spent an entire career learning new technologies and solving complex issues. Leverages experience as a Technical Expert at Apple to build positive relationships with new and existing customers and offer tailored services helping them tackle technical problems. Transitioning from customer service to software engineering, demonstrates accessible knowledge of code to ask the right questions to find the right answers and provide a higher level of client support.

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python
- **Frameworks:** React, Node.js, Django, Express.js
- Databases: MongoDB, Mongoose, PostgreSQL
- Tools: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Postman, Terminal

PROJECTS

InstaKidz | https://github.com/Cosmic-Binturongs/InstaKidz

Dates (May. 2022 – May. 2022)

- Web application that provides an Instagram experience for people under the age of 13
- Built using Figma, and utilizes Python & Django for authentication, PostgreSQL to handle the database models, React for visually functional components and dynamically rendered states, and lastly Amazon S3 for image hosting.

The Snake Game | https://github.com/Linkevin1997/Snake-Game

Dates (March 2022 – March 2022)

- Utilized HTML, CSS and JavaScript to build the Snake Game.
- Collaborated with team members to spot and debug any errors before product launch

EXPERIENCE

Apple, Inc. Elmhurst, NY

Technical Expert

Nov 2021 - Present

- Maintain and update support information and actions in the IT ticketing system, including procedural documentation and relevant reports.
- Maintain an in-depth understanding of systematic troubleshooting for MacOS and iOS.
- Deliver technical support at the Genius Bar, managing failure analysis escalations.
- Perform repairs on all Apple devices.
- Provide in-store troubleshooting and assist employees with internal store issues.

General Assembly

New York, NY

Software Engineering Apprentice

Feb 2022 – May 2022

- Completed a 13 weeklong training program dedicated to preparing students to think like engineers and approach problems creatively in order to build the next generation of web applications and digital products.
- Build 10 comprehensive full stack web applications, gain experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, EJS, Node.js, Express, React, Python, and PSQL.

EDUCATION

Cornell University, Web Design and Development Certificate/ New York, NY General Assembly, Software Engineering Immersive | New York, NY Queens College, City University of New York, BA, Economics | Flushing, NY

July. 2020- Present Jan. 2022 – Apr. 2022 Aug. 2017 – May. 2021